[
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_001",
        "back": "cry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_002",
        "back": "drive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_003",
        "back": "funny",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_004",
        "back": "hope",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_005",
        "back": "laugh",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_006",
        "back": "nice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_007",
        "back": "smile",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_008",
        "back": "strong",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_009",
        "back": "student",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_010",
        "back": "young",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_011",
        "back": "big",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_012",
        "back": "boy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_013",
        "back": "child",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_014",
        "back": "have",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_015",
        "back": "loud",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_016",
        "back": "story",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_017",
        "back": "swim",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_018",
        "back": "today",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_019",
        "back": "watch",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_020",
        "back": "worry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_021",
        "back": "able",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_022",
        "back": "alone",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_023",
        "back": "animal",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_024",
        "back": "become",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_025",
        "back": "call",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_026",
        "back": "catch",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_027",
        "back": "country",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_028",
        "back": "monkey",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_029",
        "back": "thin",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_030",
        "back": "word",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_031",
        "back": "baby",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_032",
        "back": "clean",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_033",
        "back": "eat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_034",
        "back": "enjoy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_035",
        "back": "family",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_036",
        "back": "fruit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_037",
        "back": "jump",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_038",
        "back": "kind",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_039",
        "back": "man",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_040",
        "back": "parent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_041",
        "back": "address",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_042",
        "back": "afternoon",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_043",
        "back": "come",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_044",
        "back": "home",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_045",
        "back": "letter",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_046",
        "back": "lunch",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_047",
        "back": "make",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_048",
        "back": "need",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_049",
        "back": "people",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_050",
        "back": "start",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_051",
        "back": "cook",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_052",
        "back": "day",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_053",
        "back": "drink",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_054",
        "back": "front",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_055",
        "back": "great",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_056",
        "back": "play",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_057",
        "back": "see",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_058",
        "back": "send",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_059",
        "back": "small",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_060",
        "back": "time",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_061",
        "back": "again",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_062",
        "back": "bad",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_063",
        "back": "buy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_064",
        "back": "end",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_065",
        "back": "find",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_066",
        "back": "friend",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_067",
        "back": "say",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_068",
        "back": "speak",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_069",
        "back": "sweet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_070",
        "back": "true",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_071",
        "back": "answer",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_072",
        "back": "learn",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_073",
        "back": "like",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_074",
        "back": "long",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_075",
        "back": "minute",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_076",
        "back": "sing",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_077",
        "back": "sit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_078",
        "back": "star",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_079",
        "back": "think",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_080",
        "back": "town",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_081",
        "back": "breakfast",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_082",
        "back": "carry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_083",
        "back": "cheap",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_084",
        "back": "count",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_085",
        "back": "cut",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_086",
        "back": "early",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_087",
        "back": "finish",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_088",
        "back": "flower",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_089",
        "back": "food",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_090",
        "back": "vegetable",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_091",
        "back": "begin",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_092",
        "back": "excuse",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_093",
        "back": "heavy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_094",
        "back": "market",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_095",
        "back": "meat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_096",
        "back": "money",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_097",
        "back": "put",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_098",
        "back": "station",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_099",
        "back": "visit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_100",
        "back": "yesterday",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_101",
        "back": "cold",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_102",
        "back": "dark",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_103",
        "back": "dinner",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_104",
        "back": "dish",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_105",
        "back": "evening",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_106",
        "back": "sick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_107",
        "back": "snowy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_108",
        "back": "sugar",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_109",
        "back": "tea",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_110",
        "back": "world",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_111",
        "back": "hard",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_112",
        "back": "late",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_113",
        "back": "life",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_114",
        "back": "look",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_115",
        "back": "love",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_116",
        "back": "night",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_117",
        "back": "same",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_118",
        "back": "sleep",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_119",
        "back": "water",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_120",
        "back": "weak",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_121",
        "back": "fine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_122",
        "back": "give",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_123",
        "back": "help",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_124",
        "back": "hour",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_125",
        "back": "meet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_126",
        "back": "page",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_127",
        "back": "pay",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_128",
        "back": "rain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_129",
        "back": "sell",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_130",
        "back": "tree",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_131",
        "back": "chair",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_132",
        "back": "hear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_133",
        "back": "number",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_134",
        "back": "park",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_135",
        "back": "poor",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_136",
        "back": "ready",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_137",
        "back": "ride",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_138",
        "back": "table",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_139",
        "back": "work",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_140",
        "back": "write",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_141",
        "back": "door",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_142",
        "back": "easy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_143",
        "back": "grow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_144",
        "back": "hate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_145",
        "back": "morning",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_146",
        "back": "music",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_147",
        "back": "o'clock",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_148",
        "back": "ring",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_149",
        "back": "stop",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_150",
        "back": "study",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_151",
        "back": "mirror",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_152",
        "back": "nurse",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_153",
        "back": "pocket",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_154",
        "back": "pretty",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_155",
        "back": "problem",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_156",
        "back": "pull",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_157",
        "back": "sad",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_158",
        "back": "try",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_159",
        "back": "want",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_160",
        "back": "wrong",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_161",
        "back": "high",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_162",
        "back": "keep",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_163",
        "back": "know",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_164",
        "back": "let",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_165",
        "back": "move",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_166",
        "back": "pass",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_167",
        "back": "point",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_168",
        "back": "push",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_169",
        "back": "quick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_170",
        "back": "together",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_171",
        "back": "fall",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_172",
        "back": "lady",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_173",
        "back": "rest",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_174",
        "back": "run",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_175",
        "back": "season",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_176",
        "back": "short",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_177",
        "back": "sky",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_178",
        "back": "stand",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_179",
        "back": "tall",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_180",
        "back": "wear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_181",
        "back": "bottle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_182",
        "back": "change",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_183",
        "back": "cool",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_184",
        "back": "cover",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_185",
        "back": "dry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_186",
        "back": "egg",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_187",
        "back": "expensive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_188",
        "back": "fast",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_189",
        "back": "fish",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_190",
        "back": "knife",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_191",
        "back": "full",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_192",
        "back": "garden",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_193",
        "back": "hot",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_194",
        "back": "ill",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_195",
        "back": "kitchen",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_196",
        "back": "light",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_197",
        "back": "milk",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_198",
        "back": "potato",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_199",
        "back": "warm",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_200",
        "back": "wash",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_201",
        "back": "beautiful",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_202",
        "back": "bicycle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_203",
        "back": "city",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_204",
        "back": "east",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_205",
        "back": "far",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_206",
        "back": "map",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_207",
        "back": "open",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_208",
        "back": "road",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_209",
        "back": "shoe",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_210",
        "back": "side",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_211",
        "back": "air",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_212",
        "back": "fly",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_213",
        "back": "half",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_214",
        "back": "left",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_215",
        "back": "little",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_216",
        "back": "new",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_217",
        "back": "shop",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_218",
        "back": "show",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_219",
        "back": "use",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_220",
        "back": "wait",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_221",
        "back": "ask",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_222",
        "back": "break",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_223",
        "back": "desk",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_224",
        "back": "seat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_225",
        "back": "stairs",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_226",
        "back": "stay",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_227",
        "back": "talk",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_228",
        "back": "understand",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_229",
        "back": "walk",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_230",
        "back": "year",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_231",
        "back": "act",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_232",
        "back": "bring",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_233",
        "back": "glad",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_234",
        "back": "lesson",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_235",
        "back": "listen",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_236",
        "back": "pencil",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_237",
        "back": "question",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_238",
        "back": "right",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_239",
        "back": "teach",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_240",
        "back": "way",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_241",
        "back": "angry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_242",
        "back": "boring",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_243",
        "back": "class",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_244",
        "back": "dream",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_245",
        "back": "famous",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_246",
        "back": "feel",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_247",
        "back": "future",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_248",
        "back": "group",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_249",
        "back": "hobby",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_250",
        "back": "job",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_251",
        "back": "hundred",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_252",
        "back": "invite",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_253",
        "back": "math",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_254",
        "back": "photograph (photo)",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_255",
        "back": "president",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_256",
        "back": "really",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_257",
        "back": "speech",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_258",
        "back": "travel",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_259",
        "back": "voice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_260",
        "back": "wonder",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_261",
        "back": "baseball",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_262",
        "back": "basketball",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_263",
        "back": "dangerous",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_264",
        "back": "excited",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_265",
        "back": "hill",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_266",
        "back": "hit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_267",
        "back": "hospital",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_268",
        "back": "hurt",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_269",
        "back": "motorbike",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_270",
        "back": "slow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_271",
        "back": "drop",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_272",
        "back": "earth",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_273",
        "back": "flag",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_274",
        "back": "foolish",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_275",
        "back": "hold",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_276",
        "back": "matter",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_277",
        "back": "round",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_278",
        "back": "take",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_279",
        "back": "tie",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_280",
        "back": "weather",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_281",
        "back": "art",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_282",
        "back": "build",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_283",
        "back": "choose",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_284",
        "back": "draw",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_285",
        "back": "kid",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_286",
        "back": "paint",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_287",
        "back": "picture",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_288",
        "back": "plant",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_289",
        "back": "repeat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_290",
        "back": "wall",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_291",
        "back": "absent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_292",
        "back": "back",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_293",
        "back": "fix",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_294",
        "back": "land",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_295",
        "back": "pants",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_296",
        "back": "picnic",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_297",
        "back": "river",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_298",
        "back": "rock",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_299",
        "back": "school",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_300",
        "back": "wood",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_301",
        "back": "book",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_302",
        "back": "example",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_303",
        "back": "glue",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_304",
        "back": "library",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_305",
        "back": "mean",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_306",
        "back": "piece",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_307",
        "back": "plan",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_308",
        "back": "quiet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_309",
        "back": "read",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_310",
        "back": "sound",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_311",
        "back": "correct",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_312",
        "back": "difference",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_313",
        "back": "difficult",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_314",
        "back": "excellent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_315",
        "back": "guess",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_316",
        "back": "museum",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_317",
        "back": "noise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_318",
        "back": "relax",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_319",
        "back": "science",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_320",
        "back": "tomorrow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_321",
        "back": "close",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_322",
        "back": "grass",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_323",
        "back": "hat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_324",
        "back": "lake",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_325",
        "back": "moon",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_326",
        "back": "mountain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_327",
        "back": "smell",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_328",
        "back": "soap",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_329",
        "back": "toilet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_330",
        "back": "wet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_331",
        "back": "boot",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_332",
        "back": "deep",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_333",
        "back": "farm",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_334",
        "back": "glove",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_335",
        "back": "house",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_336",
        "back": "sunny",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_337",
        "back": "top",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_338",
        "back": "well",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_339",
        "back": "wide",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_340",
        "back": "windy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_341",
        "back": "care",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_342",
        "back": "die",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_343",
        "back": "empty",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_344",
        "back": "feed",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_345",
        "back": "health",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_346",
        "back": "heart",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_347",
        "back": "large",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_348",
        "back": "remember",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_349",
        "back": "rule",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_350",
        "back": "zoo",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_351",
        "back": "dirty",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_352",
        "back": "fill",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_353",
        "back": "fresh",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_354",
        "back": "frog",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_355",
        "back": "girl",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_356",
        "back": "glass",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_357",
        "back": "hungry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_358",
        "back": "spoon",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_359",
        "back": "thirsty",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_360",
        "back": "window",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_361",
        "back": "ago",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_362",
        "back": "agree",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_363",
        "back": "beach",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_364",
        "back": "cap",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_365",
        "back": "fat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_366",
        "back": "sea",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_367",
        "back": "throw",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_368",
        "back": "towel",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_369",
        "back": "trip",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_370",
        "back": "vacation",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_371",
        "back": "ball",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_372",
        "back": "basket",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_373",
        "back": "boat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_374",
        "back": "holiday",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_375",
        "back": "lamp",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_376",
        "back": "last",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_377",
        "back": "past",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_378",
        "back": "ship",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_379",
        "back": "spend",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_380",
        "back": "west",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_381",
        "back": "beef",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_382",
        "back": "best",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_383",
        "back": "bread",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_384",
        "back": "free",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_385",
        "back": "hurry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_386",
        "back": "join",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_387",
        "back": "middle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_388",
        "back": "pair",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_389",
        "back": "pick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_390",
        "back": "store",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_391",
        "back": "bag",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_392",
        "back": "dear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_393",
        "back": "live",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_394",
        "back": "low",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_395",
        "back": "month",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_396",
        "back": "name",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_397",
        "back": "phone",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_398",
        "back": "rice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_399",
        "back": "rich",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_400",
        "back": "size",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_401",
        "back": "birth",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_402",
        "back": "clothes",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_403",
        "back": "cost",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_404",
        "back": "hide",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_405",
        "back": "pet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_406",
        "back": "puppy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_407",
        "back": "soft",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_408",
        "back": "touch",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_409",
        "back": "weigh",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_410",
        "back": "wish",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_411",
        "back": "age",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_412",
        "back": "bath",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_413",
        "back": "bright",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_414",
        "back": "brush",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_415",
        "back": "lose",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_416",
        "back": "second",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_417",
        "back": "tell",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_418",
        "back": "test",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_419",
        "back": "thank",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_420",
        "back": "ugly",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_421",
        "back": "calendar",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_422",
        "back": "dance",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_423",
        "back": "date",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_424",
        "back": "idea",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_425",
        "back": "luck",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_426",
        "back": "paper",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_427",
        "back": "post",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_428",
        "back": "receive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_429",
        "back": "toy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_430",
        "back": "week",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_431",
        "back": "clear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_432",
        "back": "continue",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_433",
        "back": "fan",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_434",
        "back": "favorite",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_435",
        "back": "floor",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_436",
        "back": "polite",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_437",
        "back": "practice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_438",
        "back": "present",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_439",
        "back": "train",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_440",
        "back": "turn",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_441",
        "back": "balloon",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_442",
        "back": "bridge",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_443",
        "back": "busy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_444",
        "back": "company",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_445",
        "back": "congratulate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_446",
        "back": "delicious",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_447",
        "back": "fight",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_448",
        "back": "old",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_449",
        "back": "restaurant",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_450",
        "back": "surprise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_451",
        "back": "gentleman",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_452",
        "back": "handsome",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_453",
        "back": "husband",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_454",
        "back": "interested",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_455",
        "back": "king",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_456",
        "back": "queen",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_457",
        "back": "skirt",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_458",
        "back": "wake",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_459",
        "back": "wife",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_460",
        "back": "woman",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_461",
        "back": "arrive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_462",
        "back": "car",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_463",
        "back": "forget",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_464",
        "back": "gate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_465",
        "back": "grand",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_466",
        "back": "line",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_467",
        "back": "subway",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_468",
        "back": "theater",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_469",
        "back": "thousand",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_470",
        "back": "win",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_471",
        "back": "cloudy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_472",
        "back": "north",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_473",
        "back": "office",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_474",
        "back": "plate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_475",
        "back": "police",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_476",
        "back": "south",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_477",
        "back": "square",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_478",
        "back": "street",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_479",
        "back": "tonight",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_480",
        "back": "umbrella",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_481",
        "back": "burn",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_482",
        "back": "exchange",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_483",
        "back": "introduce",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_484",
        "back": "offer",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_485",
        "back": "pardon",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_486",
        "back": "popular",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_487",
        "back": "prepare",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_488",
        "back": "reason",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_489",
        "back": "shake",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_490",
        "back": "shy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_491",
        "back": "bell",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_492",
        "back": "block",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_493",
        "back": "borrow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_494",
        "back": "bowl",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_495",
        "back": "confuse",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_496",
        "back": "knock",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_497",
        "back": "result",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_498",
        "back": "seem",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_499",
        "back": "smart",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_500",
        "back": "subject",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_501",
        "back": "active",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_502",
        "back": "believe",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_503",
        "back": "environment",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_504",
        "back": "forest",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_505",
        "back": "human",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_506",
        "back": "hunt",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_507",
        "back": "path",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_508",
        "back": "safe",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_509",
        "back": "service",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_510",
        "back": "wild",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_511",
        "back": "area",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_512",
        "back": "choice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_513",
        "back": "enter",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_514",
        "back": "important",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_515",
        "back": "lie",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_516",
        "back": "mad",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_517",
        "back": "nature",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_518",
        "back": "protect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_519",
        "back": "shout",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_520",
        "back": "usually",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_521",
        "back": "amazing",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_522",
        "back": "attend",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_523",
        "back": "event",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_524",
        "back": "express",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_525",
        "back": "grade",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_526",
        "back": "part",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_527",
        "back": "save",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_528",
        "back": "set",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_529",
        "back": "space",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_530",
        "back": "special",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_531",
        "back": "cheer",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_532",
        "back": "contest",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_533",
        "back": "gift",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_534",
        "back": "magazine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_535",
        "back": "perform",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_536",
        "back": "public",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_537",
        "back": "scene",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_538",
        "back": "secret",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_539",
        "back": "stage",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_540",
        "back": "unique",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_541",
        "back": "electricity",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_542",
        "back": "fact",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_543",
        "back": "fold",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_544",
        "back": "key",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_545",
        "back": "mind",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_546",
        "back": "power",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_547",
        "back": "sock",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_548",
        "back": "solve",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_549",
        "back": "stick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_550",
        "back": "traffic",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_551",
        "back": "advice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_552",
        "back": "case",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_553",
        "back": "exam",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_554",
        "back": "happen",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_555",
        "back": "lazy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_556",
        "back": "message",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_557",
        "back": "stupid",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_558",
        "back": "succeed",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_559",
        "back": "terrible",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_560",
        "back": "upset",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_561",
        "back": "airplane",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_562",
        "back": "airport",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_563",
        "back": "culture",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_564",
        "back": "decide",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_565",
        "back": "leave",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_566",
        "back": "modern",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_567",
        "back": "order",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_568",
        "back": "sand",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_569",
        "back": "spot",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_570",
        "back": "strange",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_571",
        "back": "bill",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_572",
        "back": "blow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_573",
        "back": "century",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_574",
        "back": "custom",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_575",
        "back": "experience",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_576",
        "back": "international",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_577",
        "back": "island",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_578",
        "back": "journey",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_579",
        "back": "meal",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_580",
        "back": "return",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_581",
        "back": "actually",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_582",
        "back": "camp",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_583",
        "back": "collect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_584",
        "back": "form",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_585",
        "back": "kick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_586",
        "back": "reach",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_587",
        "back": "review",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_588",
        "back": "simple",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_589",
        "back": "soccer",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_590",
        "back": "symbol",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_591",
        "back": "allow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_592",
        "back": "bat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_593",
        "back": "exercise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_594",
        "back": "force",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_595",
        "back": "leaf",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_596",
        "back": "member",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_597",
        "back": "real",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_598",
        "back": "sign",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_599",
        "back": "step",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_600",
        "back": "treat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_601",
        "back": "afraid",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_602",
        "back": "fair",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_603",
        "back": "focus",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_604",
        "back": "foreign",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_605",
        "back": "habit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_606",
        "back": "invent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_607",
        "back": "language",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_608",
        "back": "nation",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_609",
        "back": "still",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_610",
        "back": "wise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_611",
        "back": "audience",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_612",
        "back": "college",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_613",
        "back": "comfortable",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_614",
        "back": "honest",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_615",
        "back": "imagine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_616",
        "back": "level",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_617",
        "back": "sentence",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_618",
        "back": "stress",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_619",
        "back": "suddenly",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_620",
        "back": "topic",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_621",
        "back": "add",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_622",
        "back": "blind",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_623",
        "back": "button",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_624",
        "back": "create",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_625",
        "back": "memory",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_626",
        "back": "prince",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_627",
        "back": "string",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_628",
        "back": "thick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_629",
        "back": "tight",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_630",
        "back": "tradition",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_631",
        "back": "board",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_632",
        "back": "brain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_633",
        "back": "celebrate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_634",
        "back": "especially",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_635",
        "back": "hole",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_636",
        "back": "item",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_637",
        "back": "match",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_638",
        "back": "princess",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_639",
        "back": "social",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_640",
        "back": "tear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_641",
        "back": "cross",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_642",
        "back": "finally",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_643",
        "back": "follow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_644",
        "back": "heat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_645",
        "back": "rainbow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_646",
        "back": "spread",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_647",
        "back": "tired",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_648",
        "back": "tower",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_649",
        "back": "unit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_650",
        "back": "vote",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_651",
        "back": "climb",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_652",
        "back": "describe",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_653",
        "back": "energy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_654",
        "back": "engine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_655",
        "back": "field",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_656",
        "back": "include",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_657",
        "back": "perfect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_658",
        "back": "rise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_659",
        "back": "shape",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_660",
        "back": "stone",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_661",
        "back": "bake",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_662",
        "back": "communicate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_663",
        "back": "deliver",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_664",
        "back": "direct",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_665",
        "back": "goal",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_666",
        "back": "history",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_667",
        "back": "inform",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_668",
        "back": "mail",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_669",
        "back": "march",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_670",
        "back": "whole",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_671",
        "back": "appear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_672",
        "back": "community",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_673",
        "back": "festival",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_674",
        "back": "interview",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_675",
        "back": "million",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_676",
        "back": "newspaper",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_677",
        "back": "report",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_678",
        "back": "sport",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_679",
        "back": "support",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_680",
        "back": "uniform",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_681",
        "back": "brave",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_682",
        "back": "goat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_683",
        "back": "hang",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_684",
        "back": "ice",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_685",
        "back": "insect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_686",
        "back": "raise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_687",
        "back": "roll",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_688",
        "back": "sore",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_689",
        "back": "tent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_690",
        "back": "village",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_691",
        "back": "accident",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_692",
        "back": "adventure",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_693",
        "back": "corn",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_694",
        "back": "develop",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_695",
        "back": "medicine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_696",
        "back": "own",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_697",
        "back": "product",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_698",
        "back": "quite",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_699",
        "back": "roof",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_700",
        "back": "rope",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_701",
        "back": "carrot",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_702",
        "back": "cause",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_703",
        "back": "experiment",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_704",
        "back": "fry",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_705",
        "back": "ground",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_706",
        "back": "kill",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_707",
        "back": "mix",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_708",
        "back": "possible",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_709",
        "back": "pot",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_710",
        "back": "proud",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_711",
        "back": "lay",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_712",
        "back": "list",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_713",
        "back": "main",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_714",
        "back": "mark",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_715",
        "back": "mistake",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_716",
        "back": "price",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_717",
        "back": "several",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_718",
        "back": "share",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_719",
        "back": "soil",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_720",
        "back": "taste",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_721",
        "back": "awful",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_722",
        "back": "crazy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_723",
        "back": "huge",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_724",
        "back": "moment",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_725",
        "back": "odd",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_726",
        "back": "pour",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_727",
        "back": "regret",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_728",
        "back": "steal",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_729",
        "back": "thief",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_730",
        "back": "tough",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_731",
        "back": "chance",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_732",
        "back": "extra",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_733",
        "back": "hall",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_734",
        "back": "immediately",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_735",
        "back": "intend",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_736",
        "back": "mention",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_737",
        "back": "reaction",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_738",
        "back": "score",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_739",
        "back": "search",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_740",
        "back": "worse",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_741",
        "back": "bit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_742",
        "back": "common",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_743",
        "back": "diet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_744",
        "back": "evidence",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_745",
        "back": "fit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_746",
        "back": "limit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_747",
        "back": "physical",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_748",
        "back": "poison",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_749",
        "back": "sale",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_750",
        "back": "type",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_751",
        "back": "amount",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_752",
        "back": "cure",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_753",
        "back": "disease",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_754",
        "back": "medical",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_755",
        "back": "necessary",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_756",
        "back": "produce",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_757",
        "back": "reduce",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_758",
        "back": "serious",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_759",
        "back": "source",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_760",
        "back": "supply",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_761",
        "back": "castle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_762",
        "back": "decision",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_763",
        "back": "empire",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_764",
        "back": "explore",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_765",
        "back": "flight",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_766",
        "back": "guard",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_767",
        "back": "incredible",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_768",
        "back": "serve",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_769",
        "back": "skin",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_770",
        "back": "southern",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_771",
        "back": "admire",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_772",
        "back": "ancient",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_773",
        "back": "attractive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_774",
        "back": "giant",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_775",
        "back": "pack",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_776",
        "back": "prefer",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_777",
        "back": "rent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_778",
        "back": "respect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_779",
        "back": "view",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_780",
        "back": "wave",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_781",
        "back": "base",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_782",
        "back": "character",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_783",
        "back": "clever",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_784",
        "back": "enemy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_785",
        "back": "length",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_786",
        "back": "promise",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_787",
        "back": "quality",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_788",
        "back": "regularly",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_789",
        "back": "survive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_790",
        "back": "title",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_791",
        "back": "adult",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_792",
        "back": "classic",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_793",
        "back": "desert",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_794",
        "back": "discover",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_795",
        "back": "female",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_796",
        "back": "flow",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_797",
        "back": "mystery",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_798",
        "back": "opinion",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_799",
        "back": "pleasure",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_800",
        "back": "publish",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_801",
        "back": "cough",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_802",
        "back": "crowd",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_803",
        "back": "curious",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_804",
        "back": "disappear",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_805",
        "back": "edge",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_806",
        "back": "guide",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_807",
        "back": "local",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_808",
        "back": "machine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_809",
        "back": "native",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_810",
        "back": "smoke",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_811",
        "back": "avenue",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_812",
        "back": "expect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_813",
        "back": "explain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_814",
        "back": "rub",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_815",
        "back": "shine",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_816",
        "back": "strength",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_817",
        "back": "suggest",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_818",
        "back": "tour",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_819",
        "back": "western",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_820",
        "back": "wheel",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_821",
        "back": "cloth",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_822",
        "back": "equal",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_823",
        "back": "fail",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_824",
        "back": "false",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_825",
        "back": "goods",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_826",
        "back": "increase",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_827",
        "back": "penny",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_828",
        "back": "separate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_829",
        "back": "total",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_830",
        "back": "wrap",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_831",
        "back": "appreciate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_832",
        "back": "avoid",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_833",
        "back": "convenient",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_834",
        "back": "customer",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_835",
        "back": "destroy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_836",
        "back": "disappointed",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_837",
        "back": "medium",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_838",
        "back": "pattern",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_839",
        "back": "trick",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_840",
        "back": "value",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_841",
        "back": "beat",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_842",
        "back": "conduct",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_843",
        "back": "confident",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_844",
        "back": "lead",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_845",
        "back": "lift",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_846",
        "back": "male",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_847",
        "back": "muscle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_848",
        "back": "speed",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_849",
        "back": "stretch",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_850",
        "back": "trouble",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_851",
        "back": "captain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_852",
        "back": "challenge",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_853",
        "back": "complete",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_854",
        "back": "encourage",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_855",
        "back": "noon",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_856",
        "back": "position",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_857",
        "back": "race",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_858",
        "back": "record",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_859",
        "back": "skill",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_860",
        "back": "wing",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_861",
        "back": "certain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_862",
        "back": "discuss",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_863",
        "back": "edit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_864",
        "back": "gather",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_865",
        "back": "image",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_866",
        "back": "material",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_867",
        "back": "positive",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_868",
        "back": "role",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_869",
        "back": "screen",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_870",
        "back": "technology",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_871",
        "back": "attack",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_872",
        "back": "available",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_873",
        "back": "career",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_874",
        "back": "connect",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_875",
        "back": "dictionary",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_876",
        "back": "handle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_877",
        "back": "major",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_878",
        "back": "provide",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_879",
        "back": "section",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_880",
        "back": "site",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_881",
        "back": "accept",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_882",
        "back": "consider",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_883",
        "back": "exist",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_884",
        "back": "familiar",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_885",
        "back": "joy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_886",
        "back": "married",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_887",
        "back": "rather",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_888",
        "back": "represent",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_889",
        "back": "root",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_890",
        "back": "society",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_891",
        "back": "band",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_892",
        "back": "fortune",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_893",
        "back": "guest",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_894",
        "back": "host",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_895",
        "back": "original",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_896",
        "back": "peace",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_897",
        "back": "poem",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_898",
        "back": "sense",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_899",
        "back": "trust",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_900",
        "back": "wealthy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_901",
        "back": "blood",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_902",
        "back": "business",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_903",
        "back": "electronic",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_904",
        "back": "influence",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_905",
        "back": "master",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_906",
        "back": "pity",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_907",
        "back": "press",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_908",
        "back": "shoot",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_909",
        "back": "signal",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_910",
        "back": "teenager",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_911",
        "back": "achieve",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_912",
        "back": "beg",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_913",
        "back": "control",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_914",
        "back": "debate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_915",
        "back": "improve",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_916",
        "back": "similar",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_917",
        "back": "soldier",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_918",
        "back": "system",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_919",
        "back": "war",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_920",
        "back": "warn",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_921",
        "back": "announce",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_922",
        "back": "bottom",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_923",
        "back": "compete",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_924",
        "back": "copy",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_925",
        "back": "exhibit",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_926",
        "back": "print",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_927",
        "back": "project",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_928",
        "back": "proper",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_929",
        "back": "select",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_930",
        "back": "sheet",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_931",
        "back": "concentrate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_932",
        "back": "maximum",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_933",
        "back": "prize",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_934",
        "back": "require",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_935",
        "back": "research",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_936",
        "back": "respond",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_937",
        "back": "spell",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_938",
        "back": "state",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_939",
        "back": "structure",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_940",
        "back": "tool",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_941",
        "back": "flood",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_942",
        "back": "gentle",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_943",
        "back": "melt",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_944",
        "back": "operate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_945",
        "back": "recognize",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_946",
        "back": "remain",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_947",
        "back": "task",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_948",
        "back": "various",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_949",
        "back": "waste",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_950",
        "back": "worth",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_951",
        "back": "climate",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_952",
        "back": "emergency",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_953",
        "back": "factory",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_954",
        "back": "freeze",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_955",
        "back": "population",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_956",
        "back": "recently",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_957",
        "back": "responsible",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_958",
        "back": "storm",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_959",
        "back": "stream",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_960",
        "back": "temperature",
        "order": 0
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_001",
        "back": "cry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_002",
        "back": "drive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_003",
        "back": "funny",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_004",
        "back": "hope",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_005",
        "back": "laugh",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_006",
        "back": "nice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_007",
        "back": "smile",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_008",
        "back": "strong",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_009",
        "back": "student",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_010",
        "back": "young",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_011",
        "back": "big",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_012",
        "back": "boy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_013",
        "back": "child",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_014",
        "back": "have",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_015",
        "back": "loud",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_016",
        "back": "story",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_017",
        "back": "swim",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_018",
        "back": "today",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_019",
        "back": "watch",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U01_020",
        "back": "worry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_021",
        "back": "able",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_022",
        "back": "alone",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_023",
        "back": "animal",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_024",
        "back": "become",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_025",
        "back": "call",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_026",
        "back": "catch",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_027",
        "back": "country",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_028",
        "back": "monkey",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_029",
        "back": "thin",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_030",
        "back": "word",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_031",
        "back": "baby",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_032",
        "back": "clean",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_033",
        "back": "eat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_034",
        "back": "enjoy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_035",
        "back": "family",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_036",
        "back": "fruit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_037",
        "back": "jump",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_038",
        "back": "kind",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_039",
        "back": "man",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U02_040",
        "back": "parent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_041",
        "back": "address",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_042",
        "back": "afternoon",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_043",
        "back": "come",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_044",
        "back": "home",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_045",
        "back": "letter",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_046",
        "back": "lunch",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_047",
        "back": "make",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_048",
        "back": "need",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_049",
        "back": "people",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_050",
        "back": "start",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_051",
        "back": "cook",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_052",
        "back": "day",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_053",
        "back": "drink",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_054",
        "back": "front",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_055",
        "back": "great",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_056",
        "back": "play",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_057",
        "back": "see",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_058",
        "back": "send",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_059",
        "back": "small",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U03_060",
        "back": "time",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_061",
        "back": "again",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_062",
        "back": "bad",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_063",
        "back": "buy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_064",
        "back": "end",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_065",
        "back": "find",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_066",
        "back": "friend",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_067",
        "back": "say",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_068",
        "back": "speak",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_069",
        "back": "sweet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_070",
        "back": "true",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_071",
        "back": "answer",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_072",
        "back": "learn",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_073",
        "back": "like",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_074",
        "back": "long",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_075",
        "back": "minute",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_076",
        "back": "sing",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_077",
        "back": "sit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_078",
        "back": "star",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_079",
        "back": "think",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U04_080",
        "back": "town",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_081",
        "back": "breakfast",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_082",
        "back": "carry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_083",
        "back": "cheap",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_084",
        "back": "count",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_085",
        "back": "cut",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_086",
        "back": "early",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_087",
        "back": "finish",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_088",
        "back": "flower",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_089",
        "back": "food",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_090",
        "back": "vegetable",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_091",
        "back": "begin",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_092",
        "back": "excuse",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_093",
        "back": "heavy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_094",
        "back": "market",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_095",
        "back": "meat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_096",
        "back": "money",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_097",
        "back": "put",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_098",
        "back": "station",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_099",
        "back": "visit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U05_100",
        "back": "yesterday",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_101",
        "back": "cold",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_102",
        "back": "dark",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_103",
        "back": "dinner",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_104",
        "back": "dish",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_105",
        "back": "evening",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_106",
        "back": "sick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_107",
        "back": "snowy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_108",
        "back": "sugar",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_109",
        "back": "tea",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_110",
        "back": "world",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_111",
        "back": "hard",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_112",
        "back": "late",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_113",
        "back": "life",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_114",
        "back": "look",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_115",
        "back": "love",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_116",
        "back": "night",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_117",
        "back": "same",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_118",
        "back": "sleep",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_119",
        "back": "water",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U06_120",
        "back": "weak",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_121",
        "back": "fine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_122",
        "back": "give",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_123",
        "back": "help",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_124",
        "back": "hour",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_125",
        "back": "meet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_126",
        "back": "page",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_127",
        "back": "pay",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_128",
        "back": "rain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_129",
        "back": "sell",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_130",
        "back": "tree",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_131",
        "back": "chair",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_132",
        "back": "hear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_133",
        "back": "number",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_134",
        "back": "park",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_135",
        "back": "poor",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_136",
        "back": "ready",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_137",
        "back": "ride",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_138",
        "back": "table",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_139",
        "back": "work",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U07_140",
        "back": "write",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_141",
        "back": "door",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_142",
        "back": "easy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_143",
        "back": "grow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_144",
        "back": "hate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_145",
        "back": "morning",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_146",
        "back": "music",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_147",
        "back": "o'clock",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_148",
        "back": "ring",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_149",
        "back": "stop",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_150",
        "back": "study",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_151",
        "back": "mirror",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_152",
        "back": "nurse",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_153",
        "back": "pocket",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_154",
        "back": "pretty",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_155",
        "back": "problem",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_156",
        "back": "pull",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_157",
        "back": "sad",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_158",
        "back": "try",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_159",
        "back": "want",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U08_160",
        "back": "wrong",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_161",
        "back": "high",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_162",
        "back": "keep",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_163",
        "back": "know",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_164",
        "back": "let",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_165",
        "back": "move",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_166",
        "back": "pass",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_167",
        "back": "point",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_168",
        "back": "push",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_169",
        "back": "quick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_170",
        "back": "together",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_171",
        "back": "fall",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_172",
        "back": "lady",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_173",
        "back": "rest",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_174",
        "back": "run",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_175",
        "back": "season",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_176",
        "back": "short",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_177",
        "back": "sky",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_178",
        "back": "stand",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_179",
        "back": "tall",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U09_180",
        "back": "wear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_181",
        "back": "bottle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_182",
        "back": "change",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_183",
        "back": "cool",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_184",
        "back": "cover",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_185",
        "back": "dry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_186",
        "back": "egg",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_187",
        "back": "expensive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_188",
        "back": "fast",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_189",
        "back": "fish",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_190",
        "back": "knife",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_191",
        "back": "full",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_192",
        "back": "garden",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_193",
        "back": "hot",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_194",
        "back": "ill",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_195",
        "back": "kitchen",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_196",
        "back": "light",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_197",
        "back": "milk",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_198",
        "back": "potato",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_199",
        "back": "warm",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U10_200",
        "back": "wash",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_201",
        "back": "beautiful",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_202",
        "back": "bicycle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_203",
        "back": "city",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_204",
        "back": "east",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_205",
        "back": "far",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_206",
        "back": "map",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_207",
        "back": "open",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_208",
        "back": "road",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_209",
        "back": "shoe",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_210",
        "back": "side",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_211",
        "back": "air",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_212",
        "back": "fly",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_213",
        "back": "half",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_214",
        "back": "left",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_215",
        "back": "little",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_216",
        "back": "new",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_217",
        "back": "shop",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_218",
        "back": "show",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_219",
        "back": "use",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U11_220",
        "back": "wait",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_221",
        "back": "ask",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_222",
        "back": "break",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_223",
        "back": "desk",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_224",
        "back": "seat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_225",
        "back": "stairs",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_226",
        "back": "stay",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_227",
        "back": "talk",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_228",
        "back": "understand",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_229",
        "back": "walk",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_230",
        "back": "year",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_231",
        "back": "act",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_232",
        "back": "bring",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_233",
        "back": "glad",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_234",
        "back": "lesson",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_235",
        "back": "listen",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_236",
        "back": "pencil",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_237",
        "back": "question",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_238",
        "back": "right",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_239",
        "back": "teach",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B01_U12_240",
        "back": "way",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_241",
        "back": "angry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_242",
        "back": "boring",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_243",
        "back": "class",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_244",
        "back": "dream",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_245",
        "back": "famous",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_246",
        "back": "feel",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_247",
        "back": "future",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_248",
        "back": "group",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_249",
        "back": "hobby",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_250",
        "back": "job",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_251",
        "back": "hundred",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_252",
        "back": "invite",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_253",
        "back": "math",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_254",
        "back": "photograph (photo)",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_255",
        "back": "president",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_256",
        "back": "really",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_257",
        "back": "speech",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_258",
        "back": "travel",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_259",
        "back": "voice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U01_260",
        "back": "wonder",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_261",
        "back": "baseball",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_262",
        "back": "basketball",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_263",
        "back": "dangerous",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_264",
        "back": "excited",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_265",
        "back": "hill",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_266",
        "back": "hit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_267",
        "back": "hospital",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_268",
        "back": "hurt",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_269",
        "back": "motorbike",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_270",
        "back": "slow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_271",
        "back": "drop",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_272",
        "back": "earth",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_273",
        "back": "flag",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_274",
        "back": "foolish",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_275",
        "back": "hold",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_276",
        "back": "matter",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_277",
        "back": "round",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_278",
        "back": "take",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_279",
        "back": "tie",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U02_280",
        "back": "weather",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_281",
        "back": "art",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_282",
        "back": "build",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_283",
        "back": "choose",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_284",
        "back": "draw",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_285",
        "back": "kid",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_286",
        "back": "paint",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_287",
        "back": "picture",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_288",
        "back": "plant",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_289",
        "back": "repeat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_290",
        "back": "wall",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_291",
        "back": "absent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_292",
        "back": "back",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_293",
        "back": "fix",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_294",
        "back": "land",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_295",
        "back": "pants",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_296",
        "back": "picnic",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_297",
        "back": "river",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_298",
        "back": "rock",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_299",
        "back": "school",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U03_300",
        "back": "wood",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_301",
        "back": "book",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_302",
        "back": "example",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_303",
        "back": "glue",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_304",
        "back": "library",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_305",
        "back": "mean",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_306",
        "back": "piece",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_307",
        "back": "plan",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_308",
        "back": "quiet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_309",
        "back": "read",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_310",
        "back": "sound",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_311",
        "back": "correct",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_312",
        "back": "difference",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_313",
        "back": "difficult",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_314",
        "back": "excellent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_315",
        "back": "guess",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_316",
        "back": "museum",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_317",
        "back": "noise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_318",
        "back": "relax",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_319",
        "back": "science",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U04_320",
        "back": "tomorrow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_321",
        "back": "close",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_322",
        "back": "grass",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_323",
        "back": "hat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_324",
        "back": "lake",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_325",
        "back": "moon",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_326",
        "back": "mountain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_327",
        "back": "smell",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_328",
        "back": "soap",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_329",
        "back": "toilet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_330",
        "back": "wet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_331",
        "back": "boot",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_332",
        "back": "deep",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_333",
        "back": "farm",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_334",
        "back": "glove",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_335",
        "back": "house",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_336",
        "back": "sunny",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_337",
        "back": "top",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_338",
        "back": "well",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_339",
        "back": "wide",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U05_340",
        "back": "windy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_341",
        "back": "care",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_342",
        "back": "die",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_343",
        "back": "empty",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_344",
        "back": "feed",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_345",
        "back": "health",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_346",
        "back": "heart",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_347",
        "back": "large",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_348",
        "back": "remember",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_349",
        "back": "rule",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_350",
        "back": "zoo",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_351",
        "back": "dirty",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_352",
        "back": "fill",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_353",
        "back": "fresh",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_354",
        "back": "frog",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_355",
        "back": "girl",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_356",
        "back": "glass",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_357",
        "back": "hungry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_358",
        "back": "spoon",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_359",
        "back": "thirsty",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U06_360",
        "back": "window",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_361",
        "back": "ago",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_362",
        "back": "agree",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_363",
        "back": "beach",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_364",
        "back": "cap",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_365",
        "back": "fat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_366",
        "back": "sea",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_367",
        "back": "throw",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_368",
        "back": "towel",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_369",
        "back": "trip",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_370",
        "back": "vacation",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_371",
        "back": "ball",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_372",
        "back": "basket",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_373",
        "back": "boat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_374",
        "back": "holiday",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_375",
        "back": "lamp",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_376",
        "back": "last",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_377",
        "back": "past",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_378",
        "back": "ship",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_379",
        "back": "spend",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U07_380",
        "back": "west",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_381",
        "back": "beef",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_382",
        "back": "best",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_383",
        "back": "bread",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_384",
        "back": "free",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_385",
        "back": "hurry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_386",
        "back": "join",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_387",
        "back": "middle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_388",
        "back": "pair",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_389",
        "back": "pick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_390",
        "back": "store",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_391",
        "back": "bag",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_392",
        "back": "dear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_393",
        "back": "live",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_394",
        "back": "low",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_395",
        "back": "month",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_396",
        "back": "name",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_397",
        "back": "phone",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_398",
        "back": "rice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_399",
        "back": "rich",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U08_400",
        "back": "size",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_401",
        "back": "birth",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_402",
        "back": "clothes",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_403",
        "back": "cost",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_404",
        "back": "hide",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_405",
        "back": "pet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_406",
        "back": "puppy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_407",
        "back": "soft",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_408",
        "back": "touch",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_409",
        "back": "weigh",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_410",
        "back": "wish",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_411",
        "back": "age",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_412",
        "back": "bath",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_413",
        "back": "bright",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_414",
        "back": "brush",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_415",
        "back": "lose",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_416",
        "back": "second",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_417",
        "back": "tell",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_418",
        "back": "test",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_419",
        "back": "thank",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U09_420",
        "back": "ugly",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_421",
        "back": "calendar",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_422",
        "back": "dance",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_423",
        "back": "date",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_424",
        "back": "idea",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_425",
        "back": "luck",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_426",
        "back": "paper",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_427",
        "back": "post",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_428",
        "back": "receive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_429",
        "back": "toy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_430",
        "back": "week",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_431",
        "back": "clear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_432",
        "back": "continue",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_433",
        "back": "fan",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_434",
        "back": "favorite",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_435",
        "back": "floor",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_436",
        "back": "polite",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_437",
        "back": "practice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_438",
        "back": "present",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_439",
        "back": "train",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U10_440",
        "back": "turn",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_441",
        "back": "balloon",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_442",
        "back": "bridge",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_443",
        "back": "busy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_444",
        "back": "company",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_445",
        "back": "congratulate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_446",
        "back": "delicious",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_447",
        "back": "fight",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_448",
        "back": "old",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_449",
        "back": "restaurant",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_450",
        "back": "surprise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_451",
        "back": "gentleman",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_452",
        "back": "handsome",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_453",
        "back": "husband",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_454",
        "back": "interested",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_455",
        "back": "king",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_456",
        "back": "queen",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_457",
        "back": "skirt",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_458",
        "back": "wake",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_459",
        "back": "wife",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U11_460",
        "back": "woman",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_461",
        "back": "arrive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_462",
        "back": "car",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_463",
        "back": "forget",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_464",
        "back": "gate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_465",
        "back": "grand",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_466",
        "back": "line",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_467",
        "back": "subway",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_468",
        "back": "theater",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_469",
        "back": "thousand",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_470",
        "back": "win",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_471",
        "back": "cloudy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_472",
        "back": "north",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_473",
        "back": "office",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_474",
        "back": "plate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_475",
        "back": "police",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_476",
        "back": "south",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_477",
        "back": "square",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_478",
        "back": "street",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_479",
        "back": "tonight",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B02_U12_480",
        "back": "umbrella",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_481",
        "back": "burn",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_482",
        "back": "exchange",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_483",
        "back": "introduce",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_484",
        "back": "offer",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_485",
        "back": "pardon",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_486",
        "back": "popular",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_487",
        "back": "prepare",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_488",
        "back": "reason",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_489",
        "back": "shake",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_490",
        "back": "shy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_491",
        "back": "bell",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_492",
        "back": "block",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_493",
        "back": "borrow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_494",
        "back": "bowl",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_495",
        "back": "confuse",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_496",
        "back": "knock",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_497",
        "back": "result",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_498",
        "back": "seem",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_499",
        "back": "smart",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U01_500",
        "back": "subject",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_501",
        "back": "active",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_502",
        "back": "believe",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_503",
        "back": "environment",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_504",
        "back": "forest",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_505",
        "back": "human",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_506",
        "back": "hunt",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_507",
        "back": "path",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_508",
        "back": "safe",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_509",
        "back": "service",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_510",
        "back": "wild",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_511",
        "back": "area",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_512",
        "back": "choice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_513",
        "back": "enter",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_514",
        "back": "important",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_515",
        "back": "lie",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_516",
        "back": "mad",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_517",
        "back": "nature",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_518",
        "back": "protect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_519",
        "back": "shout",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U02_520",
        "back": "usually",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_521",
        "back": "amazing",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_522",
        "back": "attend",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_523",
        "back": "event",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_524",
        "back": "express",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_525",
        "back": "grade",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_526",
        "back": "part",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_527",
        "back": "save",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_528",
        "back": "set",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_529",
        "back": "space",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_530",
        "back": "special",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_531",
        "back": "cheer",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_532",
        "back": "contest",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_533",
        "back": "gift",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_534",
        "back": "magazine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_535",
        "back": "perform",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_536",
        "back": "public",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_537",
        "back": "scene",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_538",
        "back": "secret",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_539",
        "back": "stage",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U03_540",
        "back": "unique",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_541",
        "back": "electricity",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_542",
        "back": "fact",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_543",
        "back": "fold",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_544",
        "back": "key",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_545",
        "back": "mind",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_546",
        "back": "power",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_547",
        "back": "sock",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_548",
        "back": "solve",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_549",
        "back": "stick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_550",
        "back": "traffic",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_551",
        "back": "advice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_552",
        "back": "case",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_553",
        "back": "exam",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_554",
        "back": "happen",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_555",
        "back": "lazy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_556",
        "back": "message",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_557",
        "back": "stupid",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_558",
        "back": "succeed",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_559",
        "back": "terrible",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U04_560",
        "back": "upset",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_561",
        "back": "airplane",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_562",
        "back": "airport",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_563",
        "back": "culture",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_564",
        "back": "decide",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_565",
        "back": "leave",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_566",
        "back": "modern",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_567",
        "back": "order",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_568",
        "back": "sand",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_569",
        "back": "spot",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_570",
        "back": "strange",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_571",
        "back": "bill",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_572",
        "back": "blow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_573",
        "back": "century",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_574",
        "back": "custom",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_575",
        "back": "experience",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_576",
        "back": "international",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_577",
        "back": "island",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_578",
        "back": "journey",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_579",
        "back": "meal",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U05_580",
        "back": "return",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_581",
        "back": "actually",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_582",
        "back": "camp",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_583",
        "back": "collect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_584",
        "back": "form",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_585",
        "back": "kick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_586",
        "back": "reach",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_587",
        "back": "review",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_588",
        "back": "simple",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_589",
        "back": "soccer",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_590",
        "back": "symbol",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_591",
        "back": "allow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_592",
        "back": "bat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_593",
        "back": "exercise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_594",
        "back": "force",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_595",
        "back": "leaf",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_596",
        "back": "member",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_597",
        "back": "real",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_598",
        "back": "sign",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_599",
        "back": "step",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U06_600",
        "back": "treat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_601",
        "back": "afraid",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_602",
        "back": "fair",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_603",
        "back": "focus",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_604",
        "back": "foreign",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_605",
        "back": "habit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_606",
        "back": "invent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_607",
        "back": "language",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_608",
        "back": "nation",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_609",
        "back": "still",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_610",
        "back": "wise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_611",
        "back": "audience",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_612",
        "back": "college",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_613",
        "back": "comfortable",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_614",
        "back": "honest",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_615",
        "back": "imagine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_616",
        "back": "level",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_617",
        "back": "sentence",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_618",
        "back": "stress",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_619",
        "back": "suddenly",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U07_620",
        "back": "topic",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_621",
        "back": "add",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_622",
        "back": "blind",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_623",
        "back": "button",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_624",
        "back": "create",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_625",
        "back": "memory",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_626",
        "back": "prince",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_627",
        "back": "string",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_628",
        "back": "thick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_629",
        "back": "tight",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_630",
        "back": "tradition",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_631",
        "back": "board",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_632",
        "back": "brain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_633",
        "back": "celebrate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_634",
        "back": "especially",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_635",
        "back": "hole",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_636",
        "back": "item",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_637",
        "back": "match",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_638",
        "back": "princess",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_639",
        "back": "social",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U08_640",
        "back": "tear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_641",
        "back": "cross",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_642",
        "back": "finally",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_643",
        "back": "follow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_644",
        "back": "heat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_645",
        "back": "rainbow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_646",
        "back": "spread",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_647",
        "back": "tired",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_648",
        "back": "tower",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_649",
        "back": "unit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_650",
        "back": "vote",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_651",
        "back": "climb",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_652",
        "back": "describe",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_653",
        "back": "energy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_654",
        "back": "engine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_655",
        "back": "field",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_656",
        "back": "include",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_657",
        "back": "perfect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_658",
        "back": "rise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_659",
        "back": "shape",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U09_660",
        "back": "stone",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_661",
        "back": "bake",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_662",
        "back": "communicate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_663",
        "back": "deliver",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_664",
        "back": "direct",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_665",
        "back": "goal",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_666",
        "back": "history",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_667",
        "back": "inform",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_668",
        "back": "mail",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_669",
        "back": "march",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_670",
        "back": "whole",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_671",
        "back": "appear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_672",
        "back": "community",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_673",
        "back": "festival",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_674",
        "back": "interview",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_675",
        "back": "million",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_676",
        "back": "newspaper",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_677",
        "back": "report",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_678",
        "back": "sport",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_679",
        "back": "support",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U10_680",
        "back": "uniform",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_681",
        "back": "brave",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_682",
        "back": "goat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_683",
        "back": "hang",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_684",
        "back": "ice",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_685",
        "back": "insect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_686",
        "back": "raise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_687",
        "back": "roll",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_688",
        "back": "sore",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_689",
        "back": "tent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_690",
        "back": "village",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_691",
        "back": "accident",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_692",
        "back": "adventure",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_693",
        "back": "corn",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_694",
        "back": "develop",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_695",
        "back": "medicine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_696",
        "back": "own",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_697",
        "back": "product",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_698",
        "back": "quite",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_699",
        "back": "roof",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U11_700",
        "back": "rope",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_701",
        "back": "carrot",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_702",
        "back": "cause",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_703",
        "back": "experiment",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_704",
        "back": "fry",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_705",
        "back": "ground",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_706",
        "back": "kill",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_707",
        "back": "mix",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_708",
        "back": "possible",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_709",
        "back": "pot",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_710",
        "back": "proud",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_711",
        "back": "lay",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_712",
        "back": "list",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_713",
        "back": "main",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_714",
        "back": "mark",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_715",
        "back": "mistake",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_716",
        "back": "price",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_717",
        "back": "several",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_718",
        "back": "share",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_719",
        "back": "soil",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B03_U12_720",
        "back": "taste",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_721",
        "back": "awful",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_722",
        "back": "crazy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_723",
        "back": "huge",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_724",
        "back": "moment",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_725",
        "back": "odd",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_726",
        "back": "pour",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_727",
        "back": "regret",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_728",
        "back": "steal",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_729",
        "back": "thief",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_730",
        "back": "tough",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_731",
        "back": "chance",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_732",
        "back": "extra",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_733",
        "back": "hall",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_734",
        "back": "immediately",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_735",
        "back": "intend",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_736",
        "back": "mention",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_737",
        "back": "reaction",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_738",
        "back": "score",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_739",
        "back": "search",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U01_740",
        "back": "worse",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_741",
        "back": "bit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_742",
        "back": "common",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_743",
        "back": "diet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_744",
        "back": "evidence",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_745",
        "back": "fit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_746",
        "back": "limit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_747",
        "back": "physical",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_748",
        "back": "poison",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_749",
        "back": "sale",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_750",
        "back": "type",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_751",
        "back": "amount",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_752",
        "back": "cure",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_753",
        "back": "disease",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_754",
        "back": "medical",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_755",
        "back": "necessary",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_756",
        "back": "produce",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_757",
        "back": "reduce",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_758",
        "back": "serious",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_759",
        "back": "source",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U02_760",
        "back": "supply",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_761",
        "back": "castle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_762",
        "back": "decision",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_763",
        "back": "empire",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_764",
        "back": "explore",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_765",
        "back": "flight",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_766",
        "back": "guard",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_767",
        "back": "incredible",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_768",
        "back": "serve",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_769",
        "back": "skin",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_770",
        "back": "southern",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_771",
        "back": "admire",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_772",
        "back": "ancient",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_773",
        "back": "attractive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_774",
        "back": "giant",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_775",
        "back": "pack",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_776",
        "back": "prefer",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_777",
        "back": "rent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_778",
        "back": "respect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_779",
        "back": "view",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U03_780",
        "back": "wave",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_781",
        "back": "base",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_782",
        "back": "character",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_783",
        "back": "clever",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_784",
        "back": "enemy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_785",
        "back": "length",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_786",
        "back": "promise",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_787",
        "back": "quality",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_788",
        "back": "regularly",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_789",
        "back": "survive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_790",
        "back": "title",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_791",
        "back": "adult",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_792",
        "back": "classic",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_793",
        "back": "desert",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_794",
        "back": "discover",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_795",
        "back": "female",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_796",
        "back": "flow",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_797",
        "back": "mystery",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_798",
        "back": "opinion",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_799",
        "back": "pleasure",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U04_800",
        "back": "publish",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_801",
        "back": "cough",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_802",
        "back": "crowd",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_803",
        "back": "curious",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_804",
        "back": "disappear",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_805",
        "back": "edge",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_806",
        "back": "guide",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_807",
        "back": "local",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_808",
        "back": "machine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_809",
        "back": "native",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_810",
        "back": "smoke",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_811",
        "back": "avenue",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_812",
        "back": "expect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_813",
        "back": "explain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_814",
        "back": "rub",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_815",
        "back": "shine",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_816",
        "back": "strength",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_817",
        "back": "suggest",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_818",
        "back": "tour",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_819",
        "back": "western",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U05_820",
        "back": "wheel",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_821",
        "back": "cloth",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_822",
        "back": "equal",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_823",
        "back": "fail",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_824",
        "back": "false",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_825",
        "back": "goods",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_826",
        "back": "increase",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_827",
        "back": "penny",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_828",
        "back": "separate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_829",
        "back": "total",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_830",
        "back": "wrap",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_831",
        "back": "appreciate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_832",
        "back": "avoid",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_833",
        "back": "convenient",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_834",
        "back": "customer",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_835",
        "back": "destroy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_836",
        "back": "disappointed",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_837",
        "back": "medium",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_838",
        "back": "pattern",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_839",
        "back": "trick",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U06_840",
        "back": "value",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_841",
        "back": "beat",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_842",
        "back": "conduct",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_843",
        "back": "confident",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_844",
        "back": "lead",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_845",
        "back": "lift",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_846",
        "back": "male",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_847",
        "back": "muscle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_848",
        "back": "speed",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_849",
        "back": "stretch",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_850",
        "back": "trouble",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_851",
        "back": "captain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_852",
        "back": "challenge",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_853",
        "back": "complete",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_854",
        "back": "encourage",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_855",
        "back": "noon",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_856",
        "back": "position",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_857",
        "back": "race",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_858",
        "back": "record",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_859",
        "back": "skill",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U07_860",
        "back": "wing",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_861",
        "back": "certain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_862",
        "back": "discuss",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_863",
        "back": "edit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_864",
        "back": "gather",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_865",
        "back": "image",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_866",
        "back": "material",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_867",
        "back": "positive",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_868",
        "back": "role",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_869",
        "back": "screen",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_870",
        "back": "technology",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_871",
        "back": "attack",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_872",
        "back": "available",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_873",
        "back": "career",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_874",
        "back": "connect",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_875",
        "back": "dictionary",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_876",
        "back": "handle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_877",
        "back": "major",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_878",
        "back": "provide",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_879",
        "back": "section",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U08_880",
        "back": "site",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_881",
        "back": "accept",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_882",
        "back": "consider",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_883",
        "back": "exist",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_884",
        "back": "familiar",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_885",
        "back": "joy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_886",
        "back": "married",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_887",
        "back": "rather",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_888",
        "back": "represent",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_889",
        "back": "root",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_890",
        "back": "society",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_891",
        "back": "band",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_892",
        "back": "fortune",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_893",
        "back": "guest",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_894",
        "back": "host",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_895",
        "back": "original",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_896",
        "back": "peace",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_897",
        "back": "poem",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_898",
        "back": "sense",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_899",
        "back": "trust",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U09_900",
        "back": "wealthy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_901",
        "back": "blood",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_902",
        "back": "business",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_903",
        "back": "electronic",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_904",
        "back": "influence",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_905",
        "back": "master",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_906",
        "back": "pity",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_907",
        "back": "press",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_908",
        "back": "shoot",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_909",
        "back": "signal",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_910",
        "back": "teenager",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_911",
        "back": "achieve",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_912",
        "back": "beg",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_913",
        "back": "control",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_914",
        "back": "debate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_915",
        "back": "improve",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_916",
        "back": "similar",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_917",
        "back": "soldier",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_918",
        "back": "system",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_919",
        "back": "war",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U10_920",
        "back": "warn",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_921",
        "back": "announce",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_922",
        "back": "bottom",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_923",
        "back": "compete",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_924",
        "back": "copy",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_925",
        "back": "exhibit",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_926",
        "back": "print",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_927",
        "back": "project",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_928",
        "back": "proper",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_929",
        "back": "select",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_930",
        "back": "sheet",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_931",
        "back": "concentrate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_932",
        "back": "maximum",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_933",
        "back": "prize",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_934",
        "back": "require",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_935",
        "back": "research",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_936",
        "back": "respond",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_937",
        "back": "spell",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_938",
        "back": "state",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_939",
        "back": "structure",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U11_940",
        "back": "tool",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_941",
        "back": "flood",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_942",
        "back": "gentle",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_943",
        "back": "melt",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_944",
        "back": "operate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_945",
        "back": "recognize",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_946",
        "back": "remain",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_947",
        "back": "task",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_948",
        "back": "various",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_949",
        "back": "waste",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_950",
        "back": "worth",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_951",
        "back": "climate",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_952",
        "back": "emergency",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_953",
        "back": "factory",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_954",
        "back": "freeze",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_955",
        "back": "population",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_956",
        "back": "recently",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_957",
        "back": "responsible",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_958",
        "back": "storm",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_959",
        "back": "stream",
        "order": 1
    },
    {
        "front": "1000BEW_B04_U12_960",
        "back": "temperature",
        "order": 1
    }
]